Atik Mahmud | CV



Rajdhani Nirjhar, 359, Rasulbagh (6th Floor) Ashkona, Dakhinkhan, Dhaka-1230

☐ +88 01749941982 ☑ atiikmahmud@gmail.com ⊕ atikworkspace.com

Career Objective

To gain utmost competence in the field of Computer Science & Engineering sector through enthusiasm, hard works, sincerity and brilliance. Quality-focused and results-driven professional seeking a position as a web developer with PHP where I can use my two years of experience as a web developer to enhance the user experience. Moreover, I want to develop my career in well-established and fast-growing IT Industry.

Skills

- O Programming Language: C, C++, Core PHP, Laravel Framework, WordPress CMS, JavaScript
- O Database: MySQL, Oracle
- O Web Design: HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, Bootstrap
- O Operating System: Windows, Linux, Mac OS

Interested Field

- O Web Design
- Web Development
- Database Design

Experience

- From 01th February 2022 to till now, I worked at Shajgoj Ltd. (www.shajgoj.com) as a Software Engineer.
- O From 17th August 2020 to 31st October 2021, I worked at Star International (www.starintbd.com) as an Executive-IT.
- O From 1st March 2020 to 13th August 2020, I worked at IOTMDCP Industries LTD (www.iotmdcp.com) as a Junior Software Engineer.

Interpersonal Skills

- O Ability to cope up with different situation & pick up new technologies quickly.
- O Good communication skills and a good team player with Co-operative and Hardworking.

Portfolio

O GitHub: https://github.com/atiikmahmud

O Portfolio Website: http://atikworkspace.com

O Company Portfolio: http://starintbd.com

O Ecommerce Website: http://starinternational.xyz

O Ecommerce Website: http://mall.dreamlandtechbd.com

O Ecommerce Website: http://shokherdokan.com

O Attendance Management Website: http://atikworkspace.com/manage

O Alumni Association Website: http://atikworkspace.000webhostapp.com

Academic Qualification

Varendra University

Rajshahi

B. Sc in Computer Science and Engineering

2016-2019

Result: 3.27 out of 4.00

Varendra College

Rajshahi

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

Passing Year 2015

Result: 3.75 out of 5.00

Singra Damdama Pilot School and College

Rajshahi

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

Passing Year 2013

Result: 4.38 out of 5.00

Thesis / Project

 CSE Alumni Association of Varendra University Supervised By

Md. Nahid Hasan

Lecturer, Dept. of CSE, Varendra University, Rajshahi

Cell: +880 1737869322 Email: nahid@vu.edu.bd

Language Proficiency

- O Excellent in speaking and writing both Bengali and English.
- O Good interpersonal communication skills.

Personal Information

- O Name: Atik Mahmud
- Father's Name: Abdul MannanMother's Name: Mrs. Arifa Akter
- O Permanent Address: Village: Bhaturia, Post: Dighapatia, Zip Code: 6401
- P.S: Natore Sadar, District: Natore
 Date of Birth: 15th November 1996
- o Sex: Male
- O Marital Status: Unmarried
- O Religion: Islam (Sunni)
- O Nationality: Bangladeshi by Birth
- O NID No. 3736184908
- O Blood Group: O+ (Positive)
- o Cell: +880 1749941982, +880 17101041141
- O Email: atiikmahmud@gmail.com
- O Portfolio Website: atikworkspace.com

Reference

Md. Kamruzzaman

Deputy General Manager

Saif Power Group

Cell: +88 01755 548548

E-mail: kamruzzaman@saifpowertec.com

Declaration

I do hereby declare that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Atik Mahmud